IN THIS NEW GAME,
YOUR WIFE IS YOUR "UMPIRE"
WEDDING - R. ELAN (A) ELAVARASAN
S. PAVI (A) PAVITHRA
Your friend is very lucky.
How many people get the chance to marry
the same girl they love?
I didn't get it.
Baby, I hope we also can get married
like this one day, right?
It is in your hands, baby.
Just say okay.
You keep saying my son
will never amount to anything.
Seeing these two
in their wedding attire makes me so happy!
See!
He actually did it!
-We've done our duty.
-Yep.
Take the akshata to bless!
Was yours a love marriage?
Love? My appa would've killed me!
It was an arranged marriage.
Love can happen anytime in life.
Yeah, yeah. Sure it will.
Hello, sweethearts.
Finally the big day is here.
Everyone knows today's a special day
for your favourite
Instagram Influencer, Purple Pavi.
In a few seconds, you're all
going to witness that special moment.
Are you guys ready?
harish_g - Create couple account soon!
pearlkumar - By the way dude,
don't tie the knot
sharan_sp777
I'm a very big fan of you, sis
-Give it, quickly!
-Drums! Louder!
go.w.th.am
Look how your life turned out, Elan
Friends_Nesamani
Oh my God!
What's happening?
I don't understand a thing, sir!
Did I blink and miss a whole episode?
Ammu!
Life was awesome until
it was just attraction, romance, and love.
But the moment that third word changed…
Come on, everybody
Atrocity
What happened?
Pavi! Pavi! Come fast.
Coming.
Switch on the TV.
The news is about to start.
It's still five minutes to eight, thatha.
-Mwah!
-Hey! Hey!
-Appa, did you take your sugar tablet?
-No.
I'll get it.
-Ma!
-Yes.
Can't you at least remind him?
What?
You talk as if
you're going to stay with us forever.
One day you'll get married
and leave… Hey!
-Why would I leave?
-Then what?
You'll stay here forever?
Get married soon! Okay?
I will see.
Appa, your tablet.
I'll keep it here.
Hi, Momos!
-Good boy.
-How is the hair style?
Appa, take Momos to the pet spa
this evening. You're free, right?
I have to meet the auditor at three.
Okay. I will take care.
Good boy!
Nobody disturb me.
I've got work. Okay?
Good morning, sweethearts.
Random thoughts… About love…
Just because
you like someone at first sight,
doesn't mean you have to fall in love.
Take it slow. Try dating.
Even if you say yes to love,
you don't have to get married.
If you don't like, you can break up.
You don't have to marry first
to understand each other.
You can even try living together.
And above all,
love doesn't have to be
only between a boy and a girl.
This beautiful thing love
has become so progressive.
But are all boys
really this progressive?
That's the big question.
Why are you just staring at the photo?
Just say yes to one girl.
Their families are waiting for an answer.
Blocked.
Why was I born?
Why did I grow up?
Yes, rooftop. Yes, done.
I am standing under the sun.
Hey, I'm coming! Hang up!
God…
Good morning.
Welcome, sir. You can go, sir.
No, no, no. Do your job. Do your job.
Okay, boss. If you insist.
Yes, I insist.
You can go now, sir.
This is how you do your job?
Check the bag also.
Sir!
There are two, right?
You are terminated. Get out.
Appa, I lost my job.
-Forgot the spicy chutney.
-What?
No, Appa. I did my work properly.
Office politics, that's what happened.
-Who?
-Wait.
-Can't look for another job…
-Your favourite chutney.
…as they cancelled my work permit.
-What?
-Let me serve you some.
Appa, is Amma there?
Your son.
Elan.
I struggled here for one and a half years
and repaid every rupee
Appa spent to get me this job.
I can't stay here anymore.
I miss our home,
your dosas, aaya's sweet,
my brother, anni, the kids…
I even miss Appa's scoldings, you know?
Let me come home, Amma.
How'd you say this all of a sudden?
How do I handle your appa?
Amma, do you know how much
I miss all of you?
Didn't you miss me at all, Amma?
Do you know how hard it was without you?
I missed you too, son.
Me too, Amma.
-You don't have to work anymore, son.
-Okay.
Even if you just stay at home,
I'll take care of you.
I'll feed you.
Don't cry. I'm here with you now.
Stay here with us.
I can't live without you.
Dear God, protect him from the evil eye
of all beings and harmful people.
Spit.
Now go take a bath!
What's this? Make the dosas nice
and crispy. Otherwise he won't eat.
Okay, athai.
-Sister-in-law, is that a ghee dosa?
-Hey.
I'm making it. Go bathe and come.
Okay!
Anna, why is Chennai so hot?
How are you coping?
Hey! You weren't even abroad
for a year and a half.
And you have already
visited us five times.
Isn't that too much?
Chithha, when are you going abroad again?
I'm not going back.
I'm staying here.
I'll get chocolates
from the corner shop.
These are gold coin chocolates!
One for each of you.
-Hey!
-Yes?
I need to talk to you.
Come inside.
Move aside. Where is it?
For Appa. Special item.
Go, go! He is also waiting
with a special surprise.
Congratulations.
Appa!
Isn't this very expensive?
Why would I think about the price
when it's meant for you?
What are you going to do about your job?
My friend Vishwanathan has arranged
a job for me in Chennai.
I'll join next week.
Trustworthy?
Appa! It is Vishwanathan!
You take care of your job.
I'll take care of the rest.
I sent you a number.
It's my friend's daughter.
She's perfect for our family.
I'll handle everything else.
You just go meet her. That's it.
Appa, what is this?
Nothing, Appa!
Appa! You forgot to send me her photo.
Why? So you can reject her saying
her eyes, ears or nose aren't perfect?
No photo this time.
-Go!
-Okay, Appa!
-I'm going to win.
-See, I won.
Ilavarasa! Ilavarasa!
Aaya! How many times have I told you?
Just call me Elan!
Take everything upstairs!
Chithha will be staying here.
I made your favourite
sweet dumplings. Eat.
Why do you look upset?
-I just landed today.
-Yes.
How can he give me a girl's number
and talk about marriage so soon?
Since I was a kid, I've believed
in Pyaar, prema, and kaadhal.
Who's this "R. Prema"?
Love, aaya.
I came here to find a girl, fall in love,
and then get married.
At least meet her first.
This love can happen there also.
How can I meet someone
without even seeing her face?
See here.
You have her number, right?
Just click on it.
You'll get her photo by default
on WhatsApp.
-Aaya.
-What?
You are not aaya, you're idea.
-You dumb fellow! Go.
-Let me check it right away.
Wow! Such beautiful eyes, nose, and lips.
Although the tongue is the real highlight!
Your fiancée is superb!
Is that enough?
You cannot decide that.
I'm the one who decides when it's enough!
Always joking.
Whenever I try to be serious,
she thinks I'm joking.
Message her and ask for her photo.
Will do it right now.
Hi! Please send your photo!
Hey! Hey! Stupid!
Is this how you will text
a girl for a photo? Give me the phone.
2K kids!
Hi, I'm Elan here.
See, she's typing.
See.
What does "Hiii" with three i's mean?
What does it mean?
It means she really likes you. Watch now!
Your DP has such a cute dog.
She wrote "thank you!"
Now, you see my "rizz"!
Now we would love to see
who's the cute owner
of the…
-cute dog.
-"I."
I would love to see.
She sent something!
Come on guys, sit down.
One, two, three.
What is this?
You can see the face
of the cute dog's owner
in person tomorrow.
I'll come wearing this outfit.
So, are you not wearing anything now?
-Dude!
-Sorry. Deleted it.
What now? Is this the end?
Life ended or what?
-Look at that nutcase. Talking to himself.
-Yeah, baby.
Let me meet her.
If I like her, I'll say okay.
Or I can act like a fool and leave.
Hey. Come.
I'm caught in the corner
Of your eye, girl
I fell in love in an instant, girl
I saw my life falling apart
My blood froze
I've clung to the corner
Of your lips, girl
I went crazy over your beauty, girl
I saw the moon up close
I saw my shadows melt away
-Excuse me!
-Sorry?
I was looking for you yesterday
Today I'm slowly slipping away
Will my love ever reach you
As love touched me
Let us come together
Won't these days last forever?
Pyaar, prema, kaadhal
It's my aaya I have to thank.
What?
I sketch the moments I like.
This is my life's unforgettable moment.
-Actually, I had no interest coming here--
-Elavarasan?
Vaishnavi.
Sorry, I'm late.
Very late.
Sorry.
Ma'am. Sorry, ma'am.
I got delayed because of traffic.
-Okay, sit.
-Sorry.
I wanna show you something cute.
Look behind you.
See.
Are you upset?
You made such a mystery
about not sending your photo.
I expected a bit too much.
I realised only after I wore this dress.
This dress doesn't look that good, right?
Yeah, it is the dress.
Then, what do you do?
I'm a civil engineer.
Around 300 people work under me.
-Wow.
-You?
-Actually, I--
-Doesn't matter what you do.
After marriage, you'll have to
quit your job anyway.
Who will take care of me?
Of course, I will. You think
I shouldn't go to work and suffer.
No?
I mean, it shouldn't be difficult
when I get home from work.
Can you cook well?
I cook really well. You?
I'm really good at eating.
Looks like we're a perfect match.
Like French fries and ketchup.
So? What else do you want
to know about me?
Nothing.
My appa asked me to marry you,
and I said okay.
If he tells me to leave you tomorrow,
I'll do that too without a second thought.
Can I tell you something serious?
Sure.
I always listen to my appa.
Because he knows what's best for me.
So after marriage,
you'll do only what I say, right?
You will.
Okay, I have some work to do.
I'll leave now.
Think carefully and make a good decision.
Take your time.
Pay the bill. Bye.
-Crazy, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
Hey! Hey!
-Aaya!
-Yes!
Wait. I'm coming.
-You are not aaya, you're idea.
-What?
The girl's family called.
-What exactly did you tell her?
-I just spoke my mind.
Why, Appa?
You amused her with your jokes, it seems.
They agreed!
I can't understand girls these days.
Joke?
It is a joke indeed. This won't work.
You'll see a girl in a coffee shop
and follow her.
And we have to find her for you?
Don't even know her address
or Instagram ID.
Stop acting like a movie hero.
Just marry the girl your appa chose.
Don't bother everyone. Understand?
Vinoth anna! Two minutes.
Stop! Stop! Go back.
I think I've seen you somewhere.
Please. Let me take a closer look.
Excuse me.
Please remove the glass, sir.
I'm confused.
Remove, let's see what he'll find.
Did a dog bite you?
Why are you laughing?
Sometimes he laughs out of the blue.
Hi, sweethearts!
We've talked about red flags
a lot so far.
But have you ever seen a walking red flag?
Listen to how this guy
talks to the girl
he's meeting
for the first time.
Disgusting.
You made such a mystery about not sending
your photo. I expected a bit too much.
Don't understand what is he expecting?
He's body shaming the girl.
Big time bully!
Bully.
Doesn't matter what you do.
After marriage, you'll have to
quit your job anyway.
Who will take care of me?
Must quit job? Don't understand?
He expects her to stay home and serve him.
He thinks a woman
should stay at home instead of working.
Misogynist.
Can you cook well?
See that? He didn't ask if she knew how
to cook. He asked if she would cook well.
He generally implies
that girls should cook.
Chauvinist!
So after marriage,
you'll do only what I say, right?
F**king Red Flag.
Vinoth anna! That's her!
She?
She's famous on Instagram.
She exposes toxic guys.
How did you get caught with her?
Who could even live with her?
Could any girl live with a guy like him?
He spoke cutely at the start.
That's the reason
I asked you to take video.
To give the couple some cute content.
Only afterwards did I realise
his true nature from the way he spoke.
He deserves to be exposed.
Ma'am, the reel got viral.
Akka! A cigarette.
Anna!
-Matchbox please.
-Anna, aren't you that Red Flag?
How much do they pay to make
videos like that?
-Hey! Look at the Red Flag fellow!
-Yes!
He is afraid.
Tell me, Sofia!
If I see you with that Elan again,
I'll breakup with you.
Did you see how he has spoken
in that video?
And he is a friend of yours? Shame on you!
Anni, coffee! Anni!
Hey, Elan!
I'm hearing that a red video
about you has leaked.
What the hell did you do?
Hey!
Dear?
He got caught?
cheems_journey
Hey! I'm a man.
Looking after me is your job.
Behave yourself!
You wanna get slippered, douchebag!
You will be single till the end.
Guys like him are the reason
why decent men like me get a bad name.
How's he going to show his face
in public now?
Shameless!
Shameless.
Find and arrest him. Rascal! Idiot!
Because of men like this,
women are scared to even step outside.
Hashtag creep alert.
Gen Z guys are embarrassing the '80s kids!
Oh, God!
I'm really in the hospital, baby.
Please understand.
No, baby.
The moment I realized he is bad,
I stopped talking to him.
He is only paying for our tea.
Too much heat. Phew!
Vinoth anna!
We should do something to her.
Ever since that video,
she stopped respecting me too.
If only I get her address,
I'll go alone to deal with her.
No other store in Chennai
-this much option…
-Come, let us smoke.
Guys, trust me, it's my…
Vinoth anna!
She is in Insta Live…
She is in ECR Mall.
Come fast. Let's catch her.
-Come, come.
-Hey, Michael.
When I asked you to take me shopping,
you said you had work.
Now, you are running behind him
like a dog?
Shall we go shopping, baby?
Vinoth anna! Come fast! Come fast!
Come!
Vinoth anna, is that the shop?
-Who is that sly-faced girl?
-One of her gang!
-Come.
-Come. Come.
-Need to piss.
-Come, come, come.
This store is a paradise for kids.
Use Pavi 143 Promo code
and get 20% discount on your shopping.
Ma'am!
That Red Flag came
to this mall with his gang.
Try to escape somehow.
I'm sorry, sir!
My frigging back is killing me.
Bro, do you have some water?
Even I want some.
Hey!
Where are you running? She is here.
Come fast. Come.
Come. Go catch her.
-Vinoth bro, how did you let her get away?
-She slapped me before I could catch her.
Hands up!
Hi, sweethearts!
This Red Flag followed me
for a planned attack.
-See for yourself.
-Now you've made this easy.
-Then I'll speak to them myself.
-Hey, don't come near.
My 50K followers are watching.
-My fans will come.
-Wait, wait.
You stay in one place.
Don't shake the camera.
Hi, sweethearts.
You all know me as the Red Flag.
But do you know who is the real Red Flag?
My appa.
He never allowed me to do
anything I liked.
I have only one wish in my life.
To love somebody and marry.
That should not be an ordinary love story.
That should be
a crazy love story where I impress her
by doing something no other boy
in the world would do.
But, sweethearts,
will my appa accept this?
Before I show him a girl,
he showed me one.
Meanwhile…
I liked a girl the moment I saw her.
After I liked the girl,
how can I give false hope to another girl?
That is why
I spoke to her like that.
You turned it into a reel
and posted it on Instagram.
That's a masterstroke.
Because of that reel,
my wedding was called off.
You can only marry the one you love?
So
I came to thank you…
personally.
Thank you so much.
Bye!
Hey!
I shouldn't have jumped the gun.
Sorry!
But just because of this, I can't confirm
that you're not a red flag.
A red or green flag can only be decided
once you know him well.
In between you said you liked a girl.
What if that girl is already committed?
If that girl is happy,
that's enough for me.
I will never forget
the first moment I met you.
Hey, Red Flag!
Can you sketch
a most liked moment for me?
Oh, so that's how it is…
I'll go viral if she sees me
It's drizzling inside my heart
When she touches me, it's a virus
Eyes become high-res
Hey, baby, I'm a fish in the sea
So shy, you've got me blushing
Are you an iCloud moon
A phone ran out of storage
My love, my desire
Pyaar, prema, kaadhal
Crazy love
Crazy, crazy love
Hug and feel my breath
Hug and feel my vision
Come feel my feet
marveles-madhu
I guessed f***er…
Hey! Give me the bag.
What do you think about live-in?
What's there in living alone?
It's a joy to live with family.
True.
You showed up in style
Elan!
I applied for content creator
in my dream company.
They called me for an interview
next Monday.
Congrats!
Can we have a party at our house today?
Crazy love!
Crazy love, crazy love
Chithha!
Crazy love
Hey! Why?
Why make your thatha sit
where the flower vase is supposed to be?
Amma, what can I do?
He insists that he will sit there.
Go. Go. Hey, go.
-Thanks, mother-in-law.
-Take a chair and sit down.
Old iron, old steel, cash for the deal!
Please take it.
Dear.
Hey! Why are you sitting?
Get up, get up.
It's okay. Let her sit.
You also sit.
What is brother doing?
Who "brother?"
I asked what the boy is doing.
I got him a job in Dubai.
Super.
But he quit and ran back home.
No, uncle.
You raised your daughter.
Can I ask her to leave you
and take to Dubai?
So, I got a job in Chennai.
Did you make coffee? It's very nice.
I don't like this coffee.
I want it strong. How many times
do I have to tell you?
I don't want coffee.
Not only coffee, she cooks very well.
My son doesn't know anything.
He never entered the kitchen.
His only reason for coming from Dubai
was to eat my crispy dosas.
He eats very well.
I raised my daughter to be independent.
Her happiness is what matters to me.
I will do whatever for it.
My son is also like that.
He will do whatever for his happiness.
Appa says I will do whatever
it takes to make us two happy, uncle.
Is it not, Pavi?
Whatever means?
Will you jump into a well if she asks to?
He's boxed in like a cheap mime!
Amma, give me the phone.
How many times I told you
not take aaya's phone?
-Okay.
-What else, sir?
Our daughter likes him.
Shall we choose a date, then?
We never asked how much jewellery
they'd give her during the wedding.
Yeah, with your son earning millions,
they'll give him 4,000 sovereigns of gold.
For him, getting married itself
is a huge achievement.
We never asked them their caste.
The two of them are in love, right?
-Yeah?
-So love is the caste.
Wow. Two floors!
How is the house?
After your wedding there will be
space constraints in that house, right?
That's why.
Thanks a lot, Appa.
You have spent
your hard earned money on me.
My money?
You have to earn and pay the EMI.
Thought as much.
Your brother has done enough. Got it?
-Is this the place for the meter?
-Yes, sir.
-AC will come here, right?
Chinnu.
Can I ask you a question?
Ask, Ammu.
How many exes do you have?
One. And it was puppy love in school.
-You?
-One in first year,
one in second, one in third year.
Three?
Why? Any problems?
No, no. Past is past.
New love has bloomed,
two hearts entwined,
greetings from our heart.
Shall we create havoc?
Atrocity!
Ata… Ata… Atrocity
Come on, everybody
Okay.
One more.
Okay! Okay!
Idiots. Is this how you behave
in a public place? Give me the camera!
Thousand-year crop
Our man lit a fire
What an atrocity
The old school rule
Was broken by him
What an atrocity
A knight on horseback
He grabbed the tiger by its tail
He's a Pro Max type
Suited, matched perfectly,
And the drums of festivity
Pi-pi dum-dum, love everywhere
What an atrocity
Times have changed
Nadaswaram and Thavil replaced are by EDM
Sprinkling rose-water replaced by selfies
Dad's money down the drain
But drones are flying high
Scenes abound whilst in love
And after marriage all is gone
The bride is like a lit lamp
Rocking the song with style
Cribbing about the sweet in feast
That's such a cringe, man
That Titanic pose
Pains my heart
Look at uncle fully boozed
Doing the twist in drunken daze
What the hell, dear?
Your appa is embarrassing us like this.
She's thousand wala gal
Look how she lit it up
What an atrocity
That Queen in Kanchi silk
Look at her playing tricks
What an atrocity
Those hands decorated in mehndi
Maybe got herself a tin, in revenge
Make-up is done, vibe is all set
Pi-pi, dum-dum, love everywhere
What an atrocity
Amma!
-Come in, mapillai.
-Thanks, mama.
Keep coming home often.
Come, Ammu.
Why are you thinking?
Give him your hand.
No, no, no!
Hey, go!
Ammu!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What happened? Amma!
Auto! Auto!
Go quickly.
Hey, where do you want to go?
Are you late for the wedding or what?
Wedding is over.
You go faster, akka.
Hey, aren't you the girl
who's on Instagram?
Are you shooting reels?
If you do, can you include me too?
Akka, this is not a reel. It's real!
Real?
Ammu! Ammu!
Ammu. Ammu!
-They are chasing us.
-Chasing us?
Hey, who's that chasing
another man's wife?
Come closer. I'll rip you apart.
She is going to the airport.
How do you say that?
She had three exes, right?
One has butted in.
Hey, don't scare me. That's Ammu.
Ammu! Ammu!
-Get away.
-Where are you going?
Hey, go away, guys.
You bloody rogues. Go away.
You call your husband.
-Akka, he is the husband.
-Hey!
He is the husband?
Why is he roaming around in shorts?
His dhoti flew away
along with his dignity.
Hey, shut your mouth!
Hey. Do you hear me or not?
Hey, open your mouth and tell me.
Why are you stalking me?
Get lost!
"Stalk"? Hey, I'm your husband.
Please leave me alone.
Did we marry just to leave you alone?
First get down from the auto.
Akka, why are you going slowly?
Please go faster.
I'm going.
Hey, go faster, man.
Where are you rushing to?
I'm going home.
Home? Then come, let us go together.
Why go alone?
Ammu, Ammu!
Look at my face and talk, Ammu.
Ammu, your actions are scaring me.
Ammu! Open your mouth and start talking.
My plants will die without me.
What?
Momos won't eat properly.
Appa needs to be given his medication.
I don't get it.
You need to go to a pharmacy?
-Tell me, Ammu.
-You won't get it.
-Leave me alone.
-If I don't get it, explain it to me.
-The two of us met, right?
-Yes. We did meet.
-After that?
-After that we fell in love.
-After that we decided to get married.
-After that?
We printed invitations, booked the hall,
arranged catering,
did sangeet and haldi,
arranged a DJ, got an entry song.
An entry for you and one for me, and then
I tied the sacred thread around your neck.
-You tied the sacred thread?
-Yes.
That's when
I turned left and saw it.
Your amma and appa were smiling.
So what?
Then I turned right.
My amma and appa were crying.
I don't get you!
I understood it well.
Look at my speed now.
VARTA  UNCLE VROOM
Hey! Start the vehicle.
I told you, no petrol.
-Start. Do something, man.
-Hello.
The flowers for the first night is here.
Do I start decorating?
Come on, bro.
Almost time for the first night.
The flowers for the first night
have reached it seems.
What happened?
As far as I can see, nobody is there.
Hey. If the bride does not show up,
will we get paid?
Don't know, man.
-What a disaster.
-Grandma, take this.
Go away. As if I need coffee.
I told you earlier.
There is a girl in the village.
-Aunt.
-They'll gift the girl generous gold.
-Not a problem.
-Here.
Be glad the first night didn't happen.
You get me?
Here. Drink this coffee.
What's happened has happened, mama.
What's the point in being quiet?
See what can be done next.
Sir?
What, man?
-Sir, payment?
-Payment without playing anything?
Play something and take it.
-We will play at once.
-What happened? When will you come?
They will soon end this.
They have started.
Rest in peace.
What are they saying in Insta?
#RunPaviRun is trending, ma'am.
They are roasting you intensely.
Look at this.
The bride who cheated
by putting on an innocent face.
Uncle's trousers came down.
The groom's dhoti flew away.
You are beautiful.
Can I marry you?
I love marriage.
I'll come.
meowdas_memes
Varta uncle vroom
-Where are you running off?
-I said I'll get married,
not come to your house.
Goodbye. Toodles.
What the f***!
There are so many laws to protect women.
But for men… Isn't that wrong?
There are a lot of toxic women like this.
-She's actually the real Red Flag.
-What?
We need to do something, ma'am.
What you did so far is not enough?
Don't all girls get married and go
to their husband's house?
How is this happening?
That the one I gave birth
thinks in such myriad ways.
Chandra!
Give her time to think.
God!
You won't see a dad like him
anywhere else.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear. My head is spinning.
Oh, God. What am I going to tell
my son-in-law's family?
You have humiliated us so much
that we can never step out.
Ma'am. Look at this reel.
She and her stupid assistant.
Cheers!
Don't yell. We could get caught.
Elan. Do you know how a wife should be?
Listen. When I get home from work,
I knock on my door.
My wife will be standing at the door
with my jaggery coffee.
I'll give her a look.
-She'll be at my foot.
-To trip you up?
No. To unlace my shoes.
Know where a wife should be?
She should be here.
-Get it?
-So his wife should also be like that?
What's your doubt? Who are you?
Who are you?
Who?
-A man.
-Yes, sir.
She showed you who she was.
Now it's time you showed her who you are.
Correct, Ganesh. Here. Take it, man.
-Drink up, I say.
-Drink.
Drink it up fully
and go to your wife's house.
Beat her up, choke her neck
and drag her back to your house
Let's go, Vinoth anna!
Come on, let's go now.
Go. Your gate is open.
-Let her know the power of a man.
-Look at his rage.
Why are you here?
I'm here to prove that I'm a man.
Oh, yeah?
Then prove.
Give me a minute.
It's been so long since he went up.
Still no sign of him.
Did he do something in his rage?
You instigated him.
If he does something,
you will be caught by the police.
I'll get caught?
-Put your leg down.
-Police!
-Police?
-No!
Michael sir. I'm drunk and on the wheels.
They will arrest me for drunken disorder.
Come on, sir. Come push this. Push, sir.
Oh, God, the SI is close. What do we do?
Ganesh, which police man
is given an orange colour uniform?
He goes in like a thief,
but comes out like the house owner.
He bought something.
He won't tell us what he bought.
-Hey! Stop!
-What did you deliver?
-We can't reveal what we deliver.
-You can't?
-The bottle piece will go up your nose.
-Anna!
-Tell us the truth.
-We don't know either.
But when I touched it,
it felt like a small square box.
A square box?
Oh, Dad, did you hear?
Oh, what an idea
Mom, you are naughty
Dad, did you see it
Shall we go home, Ammu?
We are home, Chinnu.
Not that, Ammu…
Shall we go to our house?
Chinnu!
We are in our house, Chinnu.
Ammu!
Chinnu!
Will you come to my house or not?
I cannot come to your house.
Why don't you come to my house?
Hey! She has asked him
to be a live-in husband at her place.
Let me go. We got you married
to that girl at your request, right?
Say something, man!
Amma!
My legs and arms ache.
Can you get me the medicine
for exhaustion please?
Wait, let me get it.
Come, let's go.
God knows how my son suffered the night
with no place to sleep.
Darling,
what did I touch in your pocket?
Chocolate?
Aaya, massage below the knees only.
-Hello!
-Pavi ma'am.
I'm tortured with calls from media
every five minutes.
I don't know what to say.
All the negativity is on you, ma'am.
I think you should give an interview
and explain your stance
to do some damage control.
-What do you say?
-No, Ash.
I'm not worried about Instagram.
Elan will come.
I believe it.
Brother, set it there. There.
-Careful.
-What's this, dear?
Your daughter is acting weirdly.
Who will accept this kind of behaviour?
Anna. Not there.
Look here.
Before something is decided
in our mapillai's house,
let us both go talk to them.
What's this? Like your daughter,
you too are keeping quiet.
Anyone home?
-Look at her go.
-Akka?
Are you Pavithra?
All the gifts she's supposed to take
to her husband's house are piled up here.
You've spoilt her too much.
Talking to you or to the wall
are one and the same.
Ash! Tell them I okayed the interview.
The chief guest for our show today
needs no introduction.
#RunPaviRun.
#Mrs. Marathon.
#Lady Usain Bolt.
The lady behind these hashtags is here.
Welcome to the show,
Miss…
Mrs…
Sorry, how do I address you?
Before marriage
and after marriage,
my name is Pavi.
You can call me Pavi.
Interesting.
Generally, once a woman is married,
she adopts her husband's name
as a surname.
Isn't that the tradition?
Exactly!
It's a tradition, not condition.
So isn't marriage a tradition?
So why did you get married?
I liked the tradition of marriage.
So I married.
But
I did not like the condition
that only the girl has to live
in her husband's house.
So I did not go.
Okay, madam.
But you should have thought of it
before getting married.
You're speaking up now?
Are you married?
No.
When you get married,
and it is time for you
to leave your parents and home,
then you will understand.
Okay, madam. I don't get it.
But didn't you and your husband
fall in love and get married?
We don't get it.
Your husband didn't understand either?
I'm not here to discuss my husband
or increase my Instagram followers.
-So…
-What, ma'am?
You say this,
but your husband
is very eager to talk to you.
He is on hold.
Shall I connect him?
Brother!
You should know the statistics
when you talk.
Okay!
Tell me, ma'am.
If you are not at fault,
you can talk to him, right?
Go ahead!
Connect the call to her husband.
Yeah. Hello, Elan.
Your wife is here.
You can talk.
Ammu!
Why are you shaming me and my family
by discussing this in the media?
My intention is not to shame anyone.
Then come home immediately.
Let's discuss it with the family.
What a drama, Elan.
Am I acting?
You are the one creating
scene after scene since the wedding.
Do you know how my family suffers?
Your family suffers?
Then…
what is this?
What is this?
Was it sent without you
or your family's knowledge?
This was not on our list.
Zoom on her.
What happened?
What's going on?
Arangunathan is a monkey now.
You discussed with your family
and sent this divorce notice, right?
Caught him properly there.
Turn that off!
Answer me.
Ammu!
This is some internal plot.
Definitely I have nothing to do
with this, Ammu.
Shall we send the notice?
Notice?
But my son's life…
He is my son too, man.
A notice will instil fear.
And you will get a reply from them.
Do you want that girl home or not?
-I do.
-You can do his signature, yes?
PURPLE PAVI'S INTERVIEW
NOTICE FOR DIVORCE
Baldy, I'll slipper you!
Stop acting, Elan.
Do you know how much I loved you?
Hey! I loved you more than that.
Won't you people
ever understand the love of guys?
Even in measuring love,
it's guys
who should be shown as loving
more than girls is it?
I thought you were different.
Hey! Don't give me
these feminist dialogues.
I'm a feminist too!
Then why will you not come to my house?
If I came, they would badmouth you
by calling me a house husband.
The thought of it as a disgrace
is the real disgrace,
Mr. Feminist!
Sir. Why bring your family quarrels
to a live show?
You two could have chosen
to live by yourself, right?
Why should I go live separately?
I was earning a lot in Dubai.
Why did I quit all that?
It was to fall in love,
marry and live happily
with my parents, you know?
You talk as if only you have parents.
Don't I have parents too?
Are your parents living in Dubai?
We can go see them now and then.
That's correct.
But are your parents
living in America then?
We can go see them too,
every now and then.
Hey. If you fight on every point like this
with a guy, there won't be a thing
called "love."
You have to sacrifice
some things for "love."
For that "love" that you talk about,
we girls have sacrificed
all over these years.
You don't understand a finger
on a flame will burn. Try it.
You do it once, Elan.
You be the CM for a day.
Didn't you say when we were in love
that you'd do what no other guy had done?
Are you joking?
I say it seriously.
Now tell me, Elan.
Try my post for one day!
Will you come to my house
or not?
You will understand that my chair is a bed
of thorns, and my crown is made of thorns.
What one can do and what one cannot
will be clear to you then.
Sir. Live stream is going on now.
People are watching. Give your answer.
Don't say "yes."
Don't say it.
Say, yes. Say, yes.
What?
Will you try it for a day?
If it is possible,
I'm ready.
I am waiting.
This video is sponsored
by Jaam Jaam Matrimony.
Get married and live happily!
Give.
Anna, put that in the trunk.
Aaya, why are you crying?
Am I going to Dubai or what?
Chill.
Amma!
Can you survive without Mom's cooking?1
Mom, you still think I'm a child?
I'll get going.
Call if you have any doubts.
Doubts?
-Chithha's room is mine.
-Chithha's room is for me.
Shall we go?
Appa…
Bye! Oh, no.
Are you okay, Chinnu?
Leaving an eight storied house
LAKSHMI HOUSE
Come in, mapillai, come.
Where is the place for you, oh, prince?
Mapillai a lion…
Put your right foot first, son.
Mapillai, a king, a kid
There is.
There is a big problem in this house.
Mapillai a lion, a king
Mapillai came trusting
Mapillai with no ego
Amma…
He asked for a pot
When refused, he made a ruckus
Mapillai,
I didn't know your preference.
So I made both and brought you.
One chicken, the other mutton.
Super!
Mapillai a lion, a king, a kid
He came trusting
India versus England. New player.
He too got married just now.
The little Lord's cart…
Find out what mapillai likes,
make a list and go buy.
Here. Use drumsticks and make mutton stew.
-Mapillai? Am I right?
-Amma.
-Oh, dear.
-Appa.
-That.
-Eat well.
Hey. Go switch on the AC in the room.
When mapillai goes in,
room will be chill then.
Have some drumstick curry.
Hot water. Shall I keep it in?
Police.
Thief.
Let's serve the mapillai some dessert.
Why are you gawking? Give him.
Serve him.
-Serve more. A little more.
-Elan?
-Amma.
-How are you, dear?
Having a great time here, Amma.
Amma! Amma made a biriyani here.
Who, dear?
Pavi's amma, Amma.
She added cloves and cinnamon,
and it turned out delicious.
A little more?
Amma, I'm finding it difficult to eat
while speaking. I'll talk with you later.
Biriyani always is flavoured with cloves
and cinnamon.
He is going gaga not knowing a thing.
Mapillai. You won't come to a feast
at our house, is it?
Since you did not come,
I made this for you.
Cashew pudding. Try it.
It will be superb.
So, what is your job?
He is a civil engineer.
He joins next week. Right, son?
Yes.
Brainless idiot.
-You know I like whisky with mashed eggs.
-Getting it.
Hey, mashed eggs are here.
-Hey, mashed eggs are here.
-Hey.
So the mashed eggs are here. Enjoy!
-Vinoth anna.
-What?
No one asked what the party was for?
Yes.
-Why, man?
-My wife has got her dream job.
-Cheers!
-Hey.
-Wow. Congratulations.
-Cheers!
Then, my job?
Hey, cheers!
-Cheers.
-Get smashed. Cheers, cheers.
-Akka, for you.
She won't take.
-You'll drink?
-No.
-Try taking it. I'll send you home.
-Ammu, open your mouth.
So leave all that…
What about your job?
Tell me, man.
I'll get it next week, Vinoth anna.
-Viswanathan sir?
-Tell me Elan, sir.
Well, sir, about that job…
I told you. I'll employ you next week.
Your question makes it
sound like you doubt me.
No, not at all, sir.
Just a follow-up call, sir.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, sir.
Mapillai!
Mapillai a lion…
-Were you talking about the job?
-Yes.
Mapillai, a king…
-What did they say?
-That I can join next week.
Shall I get you hot water?
I will take a cold water bath.
The broom is coming apart.
No one to buy me a new one.
Mapillai!
How long does this last?
It's a test match. Will last five days.
Okay, once you go to work,
how will you watch all this?
Do you want to see something, mama?
-No, mapillai. You watch.
-No, mama.
I'll watch the highlights.
Nadhars Grandpa!
Is it very difficult to sit idly?
Viswanatha
Alagesan, sir. Morning, sir!
Get two cigarettes.
Give me a job!
Take it!
Viswanatha
Two cigarettes.
Gimme, gimme, gimme job!
One is here.
Where is the other one?
Viswanathan sir. Viswanathan sir.
Next week, sir.
Thank you, thank you.
Viswanatha
Amma…
-Athai?
-Yes, tell.
Maapilai…
Can I get some coffee, athai?
The coffee has cooled down.
I poured it down.
There is milk near cooker.
Please make coffee yourself.
Sir!
My mind was also broken
the day this leg was broken, sir.
You shouldn't just sit in one place
like a sticky sticker, sir.
Nobody will respect you.
You should run in this revolving world.
Get up and run.
-Get up and run.
-Will run.
One day I will surely run.
If the elephant can,
why can't the cat?
Viswanathan sir.
The cat got the leg, sir!
The cat got the call.
Amma, what's for dinner tonight?
-Dosa, as usual.
-Why don't you make chapati with chana?
Okay?
Nadhars Thatha!
This is a wheelchair.
If you roll this like this,
you can walk away on your own.
Mama, what are you doing?
Will you text me the score
for every five minutes tomorrow?
I will be busy.
You should text me continuously.
Elan.
Get some water.
I'm talking to you. Go!
Ammu.
I'm at home. If you ask for water,
I'll give it to you.
If I'm busy tomorrow.
What will you do?
Did you get the job?
Did you get?
Got it!
Tomorrow, I'll be on a different level.
Chicken biryani ready, brother.
He asked for water, give it to him.
Two biryanis, two…
CHARMINAR
CHICKEN BIRIYANI
The total is Rs. 450.
Okay. Gpay…
The number your are trying to reach
is currently switched off.
Send the balance payment of 50,000 here
₹50,000 - sent to Viswanathan
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Come, mapillai.
Chandra, mapillai has come.
Mapillai, chana ready.
I will make hot chapatis.
Chinnu, how was the first day?
Viswanathan seems to be a very bad person.
He cheated me.
It's okay. This is also good in a way.
If you are at home,
take good care of the house.
Tell Chinnu.
Will you?
Yes, I will take care.
Water the plants in the afternoon
and in the evening.
Take Momos to the spa in the evening.
Tell Elan to sit behind and grab him.
Okay, Chinnu?
Don't go to the bathroom alone. Ask Elan.
He'll help.
Okay, Chinnu? Chinnu!
…trapped
Chinnu, you didn't say "I love you."
No way to return
I love you, Ammu.
Trapped, trapped in a lion's den
While looking for a chicken piece
Tank is overflowing. Switch it off.
Quickly.
Went in search of
No honour, no pride
No shame, you ended up falling
Into the water when the booby trap was set
Switch is here. Why did he run upstairs?
No stamina, no breath
On Aadi Friday, choked, and fatigued
Idi idi idi idiyappam wife
Mapillai, please iron this top
and bring it quickly.
Idiyappam! Everything has changed
You are the evidence
The whole town is talking
The new trend became viral
Amma became athai
The lion became a cat
Job in Dubai…
CSK Mumbai match
Started in the house
Do this.
-Hey Momo. Momo.
-Feed it to him.
Switch on the TV.
Idiyappam
Hurry up.
It is so hot. Cool it a little and bring.
Come on, clean it properly.
Idiyappam, idiyappam, idiyappam
-Is it okay, athai?
-No, do it again.
Idiyappam
No life, no stamina, no breath
On Aadi Friday, choked, and fatigued
Idi idi idi idiyaappam wife…
-Why are you sitting?
-I didn't sit.
Come quick.
Coming.
-Water ready?
-Where did you allow me to drink?
-Washed?
-How many times?
Idi Idi Idi Idiyaappam
Grocery list is there. Bag!
Idiyappam
-Bye, athai.
-Okay.
Uncle Murthy, let me know
if there's any good job in Dubai.
If there is a job in Dubai,
why am I here buying onions?
Who is in the shop?
Oh, you?
Okay. Pack everything in this list. Fast.
I have so much work to do.
Half a kilo of tur dal,
half a kilo of moong dal,
half a kilo of chana dal,
and two litres of oil.
Then sugar…
Half a kilo of that too?
Five hundred grams.
It's mentioned as 500 grams.
Then two Vim bars, ten eggs,
one packet of sesame seeds,
-and five kilo of rice.
-Rice means? Which one?
Which rice?
Give good quality rice.
Ponni, Deluxe Ponni, samai rice,
varagu rice, IR 8,
IR 20, kuthiraivali,
karuppu kavuni,
and so many other varieties.
Which one do you want?
Is there anything good
that you'd recommend?
What do you eat at home?
We will have biriyani at times.
Then, basmati rice.
Yes, yes. Same thing.
Why didn't you say this at the start?
Are you sure you want five kilos?
It is written as five kilos.
Give the same quantity.
Are you going to cheat by adding extra?
Look what your husband has done.
I asked him to buy regular rice,
but he bought biryani rice.
Are we eating biriyani three times a day?
If he wasn't sure, he could've
just called and asked, right?
-What, Chinnu?
-Leave it.
Don't worry, I'll handle it.
What? What are you staring at?
From now on, we'll be eating
this biryani rice three times a day.
No gravy. Just rasam.
Who is that?
Talk to me.
-One litre of imported liquor.
-Hey, where?
-In Vinoth anna's house.
-Hey, for me?
Hey! If you come before six o'clock,
you'll get it.
Otherwise, you'll only get
an empty bottle.
-Come quick.
Starting right now.
-Athai.
-I forgot to tell you.
In our area, they are giving 6,000 rupees
and two bed sheets for flood relief.
The ration card is on top of the fridge.
Green colour one.
Go quickly and get it.
Athai, I'm going out.
Do you think 6,000 rupees grows on trees?
Go get the money first, then you go.
Look, they'll give it only
until six o'clock.
Go and collect it.
I'll be there by seven.
Boss! What is the bag for?
You will wrap the blanket around you
after getting?
Boss, can I stand before you?
-You want to stand before me?
-Yes!
Hey, get lost, man!
Why would I allow that?
Michael, I have started.
Do you hear traffic sound?
I'm coming now.
-Come. Otherwise it will be empty.
-Save some for me.
Aaya, it is getting late.
Can you get it for me?
Legs hurt standing since morning,
and you want me to get it for you?
-You useless fool!
-Okay. Go.
She is scolding me.
My aaya always talk sweetly.
I miss my aaya.
-You want to stand in front of me?
-No need.
For what joy, now?
RELIEF FUND
-You are the last person?
-Take this.
-Hey!
-Go!
Take this, bro. Quickly.
It's getting late.
-Take this.
-Anna?
Take this.
Give this to the RCS Bank nearby.
-They will give.
-Anna, I don't understand.
Hey! You are supposed
to bring ration card, not ATM card!
Move aside.
Go. Go.
Please do something, bro.
My athai will knead me
like chapati dough. Please!
There's nothing I can do.
Write and collect it yourself.
Pick the phone.
Hey. I should call Vinoth anna.
Idea.
My precious.
-You remembered aaya just now?
-It's not like that.
I raised you with so much love.
-Didn't you remember me?
-Aaya, let me talk.
When you were little,
I'd sit beside you and roll kozhukattai…
-Let me talk.
-…just the way you liked.
-You forgot all that.
-Shut up!
I don't know what you'll do
or where you'll get it,
but somehow, please Google pay me
6,000 rupees, aaya.
Let me see!
You are not watching TV?
What?
Looks like the ration card
hasn't been touched.
Did you go or not?
I'm asking you only.
I went, athai.
I will Google Pay you.
Google Pay?
They won't do like that.
What, athai?
It is digital India.
Chandra!
It's cold. Please bring me a blanket.
Where are those two blankets?
You don't you know the difference between
an ATM card and a ration card?
Six thousand rupees gone.
It would have been useful
to buy food for Momos.
You are not responsible at all.
Sleep in the cold. Go!
I jumped in blindly.
Give me some idea, Vinoth anna.
I will tell you.
You know what some women usually do?
As soon as their husband
comes home from work,
they play both sides,
start complaining about his amma.
They'll not let him eat, sleep, or go to
work peacefully, pushing him into stress,
high BP, diabetes, and depression.
In the end, he either sends
his amma to an old-age home
or moves out to live separately.
Didn't understand?
Now, you are the girl.
Your wife is the husband.
Son, can you grind the coconut?
-Coconut, athai?
-Put it in the mixer.
Okay, athai.
Today I'm going to grind
this coconut in a way…
-Athai?
-Yes?
Why mixer is not working suddenly?
Oh, my God!
Don't know what happened?
-Mixer is not working?
-Yes.
Oh, my God.
She'll come and say, "I'm hungry."
My hands are covered in flour,
dear son.
Can you grind that coconut by hand?
What's the big deal, athai?
I will do it right now.
It's the grinding stone.
It's mother-in-law's grinding stone.
What happened?
Nothing…
I crushed my finger today
while grinding coconut on the stone.
Why?
Mixer is there, right?
Hey! Aunt said
you like it ground by hand, right
Did you like it, Ammu?
Amma.
I believe you asked him to grind
the coconut by hand yesterday.
Yes.
-Why?
-Mixer was not working.
Atrocity
What happened?
Chinnu.
-Chinnu.
-Ammu.
When did you come?
-Coffee!
-Keep it there. I will finish this first.
Thank God!
I was about to put this
in the washing machine.
Aunt said
this material
would get spoiled in the machine.
Give it to me.
Nothing will happen to this material.
-Then…
-Hey, leave it. Ammu.
Don't keep asking mother-in-law
about everything.
She might have forgotten and said that.
I'm thinking of it as exercise and do it.
One thump, thump, one hit.
Thump, thump, thump.
Amma, did you iron my clothes?
Maapilai, can you iron the clothes?
Okay, athai.
Ammu, two minutes.
-Amma.
-Yes?
This month's salary.
Okay, okay.
Amma.
I only asked Elan to help you.
Don't dump every chore on him.
It feels like he's slowly taking
my daughter away.
I'm scared he'll separate her
from me completely.
Don't let that happen from the beginning.
Keep everything under your control.
I had a daughter-in-law once…
She always played a double game
and took my son away from me.
Now there's no one
even to make me a cup of coffee.
Listen, Chandra, if he takes one big step,
you take a bigger one.
Hope you understand.
Pavi's mom! Pavi's mom!
What curry did you make today?
Tamarind curry.
Can you give a little for my daughter?
Hey, why don't I see you upstairs
these days?
I have enough work in the house, aunty.
You'll get bored staying at home.
Come upstairs once in a while.
We will chat while making papad.
-Okay, will come.
-Okay.
Did you put groundnut in it?
Yes, I did.
-It will be tasty, eat.
-Thanks, Pavi's mom. Bye.
-You should come to make papads, okay?
-Bye, bye.
One minute.
-Today I'm a doctor. You?
-Slippers.
What would have happened? What would
have happened? What happened?
It will be okay if she wakes up.
Ammu, I love you.
Aunty from the house above
came over yesterday?
Yes, I gave curry.
Don't you feel ashamed?
When that aunty came,
what dress were you wearing?
I have enough work in the house, aunty.
You were trying to look glamorous?
That aunty was flirting with you.
And you were chatting happily too?
My amma felt so embarrassed.
She invited to sundry papads, I believe?
Yes, she called.
Yuck!
Atrocity, what happened?
Where's the crow? It only shows up
when we dry papads.
Do you need the AC on
while you are in the bathroom?
Does money grow on trees?
Can't you even switch off the AC properly?
My amma calls and scolds me
while I'm at work.
What am I supposed to tell you?
I switch on the AC only at noon.
I switch it off by one o'clock.
I use it only because it's summer.
Do you know what your amma said? She asked
if my appa pays the AC bill.
Her problem isn't the AC.
She indirectly complains
that I'm living here for free.
Okay, okay. Don't cry.
Don't cry.
No! I can't say anything.
You start crying immediately.
What's wrong if your husband
wakes up early?
He'll wait until all the work is done,
then wake up.
She expects me to wake up
when she thinks is right time to wake up.
Why does it matter when I wake up?
I finish all the work on time.
Who dries underwear in the living room?
Guests were there too.
Oh, dear! What kind of upbringing is this?
I don't know what to do. That day
I went upstairs to dry my underwear,
your mom glared at me
because the upstairs aunty was there.
So I dried it downstairs.
What should I do? Fine!
I won't wear underwear anymore.
-Happy?
-Hey, hey. Yucky! Yucky!
The washed clothes have been
on the sofa for three days.
Should I fold them too?
I've never told you this before.
I fold all the clothes.
Then your amma comes,
says I folded them wrongly,
and folds them again.
Then why should I fold them?
He's always on the phone.
How do we know
if he's talking to a boy or a girl?
Does your amma
really think that badly?
Here, Pavi. If you doubt me,
check it yourself.
How long does it take
to enter a password?
You said your husband stays home all day.
If he's idle,
he'll keep overthinking.
Okay, I have an idea.
Give him some responsibilities.
Then he won't have time to fight.
-Shall we start? Ready.
-Hey.
Ammu! Do you know
what your amma did today?
Here's this month's salary.
I'll give it only to you from now on.
You're in charge
of everything now, Chinnu.
Happy, Chinnu?
If Ammu is happy, Chinnu is happy too.
Aren't you going to buy groceries?
-Sir.
-Hi.
Please check if everything
is correct. It looks correct.
-Thank you.
-Hello! Leaving without tips?
-Don't want?
-Thanks.
Thank you, madam.
The expense is ten
While the income is eight
Spend carefully.
The bill is important, okay?
For athai, the total is 8,000.
-What is it, Chinnu?
-Is this the costliest rice?
Then give that one.
This is fat-free for Momos.
And this one is sugar-free for you.
One, two, three, four… Take it.
Spend carefully.
The bill is important, okay?
Expense 1500, okay?
The expense is ten
While the income is eight
Hi, Ammu. My sweetheart.
Our guy is going to smash it
Bumrah bowled a no-ball
Whose wheel did the bumper hit?
Didn't keep count, didn't count the cash
Yet a balance still exists
What's this, son-in-law?
-Robotic vacuum cleaner.
-Meaning?
It's hard for athai to bend
and sweep, right? Go, go.
Go on. Mama, look! It's moving.
-Is it?
-Yes.
Hey. Sensor. Move.
What was your math score in Grade 10?
Ninety-seven.
What about 12th?
One ninety eight.
How much money
did I give you on the first?
Fifty thousand?
How much is left now?
Two thousand!
I gave you money for 30 days,
but you spent it in just 15 days.
What did all your education achieve?
You never said it is for 30 days, Ammu.
Now, you know why my amma scolds you?
You're always blaming my amma.
If you behaved properly,
why would she scold you?
What are we going to do for money
for the next 15 days?
We'll have to beg.
Go ahead. Beg and come.
Hey! Chithha has come. Chithha has come.
Dear! You've come.
Oh, dear, you've become so thin.
You got drenched in the rain too.
Look who has come home.
-How are you, son?
-I'm good.
Do you still have to
go back to that house?
Just stay here.
Starting again from beginning?
Can you help me or not?
You never listen to me anyway.
Sleep. I'll ask Appa
and get it for you. Okay?
Sleep. Sleep well.
You never seem to worry about anything.
Your amma studied
only up to eighth grade.
Even she manages
the household expenses well.
You can't even do that?
You can't hold a proper job.
Yet you shamelessly ask for money.
I'm still paying your home loan
from my pension.
Find a decent job first,
then bring your wife home.
Otherwise, don't come.
The person you are calling
has not replied. Please try again later.
Maapilai,
I admitted Pavi to school
for the first time.
I came home and changed my shirt.
She came running behind me, out of breath.
It will be around two kilometres.
She must have chased my scooter.
But I never imagined
she'd run back after marriage too.
I thought her life was ruined.
But then you came to my house.
No other man would have done that.
You did.
I felt proud.
But why did you do it, son?
I don't know, mama.
I like Pavi very much.
What did I do, mama?
Everyone thinks I'm useless.
Maapilai,
knowingly or unknowingly,
you've chosen a difficult role.
For generations,
we've burdened women with marriage.
Feeding the children,
taking care of the husband,
looking after the elders
and meeting everyone's needs.
Doing all this,
they forget what they want.
How do we see it?
We say it's just their job. Housewife.
Did they marry a building?
There's a better name for it. Homemaker.
They are the ones who build a home.
You may achieve a lot outside,
but if there is no peace at home…
My amma, your amma, Pavi's amma,
they all do the same. How?
Selflessly. With love.
You have two choices.
Walk away and go back home.
Pavi will eventually return.
After all, she's a girl.
But there's another choice.
It's harder.
But if you choose it,
your decision will show you
who you really are.
Think about it.
I spoke in anger.
No matter how much we fight,
don't stop talking to me.
I can't bear that.
Sorry, Chinnu.
Tell me.
Vinoth anna,
it's time to show who I am.
Super. Super. Wait a second.
Tell me now.
Vinoth anna!
From now on, the way I take care of
my wife, athai, mama, thatha, and Momos,
wait and watch
how much they are going
to love me in return.
Hang up, Vinoth anna.
Such a nice friend!
Athai. Come, athai.
I picked it fresh this morning.
Athai.
Your favourite chicken soup.
Have it.
The last time I came here
was with my Lakshmi.
-Nadhars Grandpa?
-What?
Up for a smoke?
Here.
I feel the love floating in the breeze
When I learned the meaning of my life
Wow!
I feel I'm newly born again
When drenched in love
When a bird finds his way back to his nest
Even the tiniest twig blooms
With beauty in that moment
I soar beyond the sky
I open my heart beyond myself…
I see the love in the air
When I learned the meaning of life
Appa, here's your diabetic pill.
I already ate.
Maapilai gave it to me.
I feel I'm newly born again
When drenched in love
What? A no-ball now?
What's happening?
-Mother-in-law! Our team's batting.
-Then that's fine.
-I didn't know.
-It's a free hit.
Buddy.
Can I keep it here?
-Okay. I'm leaving, anni.
-Eat with us, Elan.
She'll be home. I have to cook.
Cook?
-Hi, sweethearts!
-Are you cooking?
-For me?
-It's all for you.
How sweet!
Best husband ever.
Even the little leaves
That drifts along a stream
Find their way to the shore through
Countless gentle collisions
When one path comes to an end
A new path begins to unfold
Slowly, the dawn begins to break
Nothing lasts forever
Let's live and move forward
Let us find love before we go
As the years drift toward the horizon
Where are we bound?
Let us just carry love with us
The wave that touches is also love
Come here.
-What?
-Come on. It's okay, sit here.
I have made a special dosa for you.
-Have it.
-Okay.
I make crispy dosa to all.
But, by the time
I get ready to eat,
after setting up the table and all that,
it will become cold and soggy.
The last time I ate a crispy dosa
was before my marriage.
Athai, are you married?
Honestly, you don't look like that.
You look like Pavi's younger akka.
Amma, when did you come?
Can't you inform before coming?
No one is here now, you know?
Wait here.
Let me finish this work and come.
How are the kids? It's been a long time
since I spoke to anni.
I'll be right there.
Amma, can I make a coffee for you?
Wait, I'll come.
Have this.
What am I seeing?
What are you looking at?
Have the coffee.
Change the dress first.
What nonsense is this?
We're having a hard time
worrying about you.
Have you thought about that?
Your appa went out of his way
and got a job for you.
I'm here to share that news with you.
Go to work properly
and just be like normal people.
I got a raise. 35,000.
I too got a job.
-Congrats.
-25,000 salary.
I have to start from Monday.
-Chinnu.
-Yeah?
Do you really need
to take up a job with such low pay?
You take such good care of Amma, Appa,
and thatha while you're at home.
I feel so secure, you know?
Is there a need that the family will run
only if you go to this job?
You deserve a much better job, Elan.
But if you are okay with this,
I don't want to stop you.
-Amma.
-Elan.
I hope you are starting
the job from Monday?
No, Amma, me and Pavi
discussed about this.
This job won't suit me.
Convince Appa, please.
Okay, dear. I will take care.
He will join for sure. I will see to that.
Get the vehicle, now.
You come by car.
Can't you bring her early?
Don't you know that regular
health checkups are a must at this age?
Uncle, I'm asking you only.
Man, just spit the fact out.
Seven blockages. It's a complicated case.
Seven blockages?
So, open-heart surgery
is needed right away?
Are you a doctor? Tell me?
What did the doctor say?
Doctor, is everything fine?
Mummy, your daughter-in-law is no joke.
Her arguments are spot on, right?
Man, she's really going to tear into you.
What, did she figure it out?
I had a tough time managing her.
Why are you stressing out?
Let us hold it for some more time.
Soon she will stop thinking.
Come on, let's play Uno.
Michael, Its time. Bring them in.
Okay. Are you ready, mummy?
You're just eating peanuts
and acting so much?
Don't overdo it.
You got the treatment
and now you are stable.
Just stick to the script.
-Enough?
-Actor Savitri is no more. So?
Go.
Michael, ensure my husband is not coming.
He'll read it right off my face.
Send him to the pharmacy for something.
-Right.
-He's never done anything for me so far.
She's a little more stable now.
Let's wait and see.
Not everyone can go inside.
Only two important family members
can go in to see her.
Hello, where are you going?
I want to see her.
You go and buy this medicine first.
You two, go and visit her.
You can get that only in Tambaram.
Be quick.
Yes, Tambaram or Thanjavur.
Get it quickly.
Hi, Vinoth Uncle.
I'm not Vinoth.
I'm Dr. Sithar Bootham, okay?
Yeah, you do look like a goblin. Carry on.
Growing up just like thatha.
Little devils.
I got scared, son,
about whether I'd be able
to see you all again.
I never expected I'd get a heart attack.
Why is all this happening
only to our family?
Elan, please, be outside for a while.
Go.
Pavi.
I was losing my mind
without you and Elan staying with us.
I have only one desire left.
Can I ask you something like my daughter?
Please.
I just wish I could stay with you all.
I don't know how long I will survive.
Can you stay with us for a few days?
Mummy
Forget it, she is destined to
I heard you opted to work from home.
He said your raise was revoked too.
Am I troubling you too much?
No, aunty, don't you worry about that.
Take care of your health first.
That's the priority.
Son, why don't you join the job
your appa suggested?
With extra earning,
Pavi will get some relief from her burden.
What are you thinking about?
Now I have two daughters-in-law
who are like my own daughters.
Pavi, tell him.
He will listen to you only.
…O-flex, oh, no
Flex-o-flex, flex-o-flex
Mummy
Drama, drama, drama queen
Enough overacting now
You have overtaken our watermelon star
Your performance exceeds reel after reel
If you scold her, that's it
She's from the con girl batch
She's devising a plan
My my
Pal's fallen, very stylish, man
She would not even stand a Vicks tablet
Flex-o-flex, flex-o-flex
Oh no, flex-o-flex, flex-o-flex
Flex-o-flex, oh no!
Flex-o-flex, flex-o-flex
Flex-o-flex, flex-o-flex, oh no!
She got caught
While trying to set things up while single
Just checking the vibe
And now she's trapped at home
Hey! A real-life Squid Game has begun
Tug-of-war now is getting intense
Planted a seed, planted a seed
Enough is enough, Pavi.
We have decided to downsize the company.
We need full time employees only.
Good luck.
Mummy has won!
Spider-Man!
Hey, hey.
-What happened?
-Nothing.
Escape.
Michael, Michael.
Can I see aunty's medical reports?
Ashiq's appa is a cardiologist.
We can go for a second opinion.
You need the reports?
I'll get them printed.
What to do now?
Hands please.
How is the work?
Is the work load heavy?
I got used to it now.
Mummy, the fake reports are all set.
You just maintain your act.
Be careful now,
or else she will figure it out.
Bye, mummy.
Delete this voice note immediately.
God. Leave me out of this.
Amma, what is this?
I thought you will leave us, Amma.
You scared me.
You left me already, dear.
Without you here,
I was only a living corpse.
In your search for a good life,
you left me behind.
Even you never thought about me, son.
Please stop, aunty.
I treated you like my amma.
And all of you were pretending.
No one has ever fooled me like this.
You hurt me, aunty.
I didn't expect you would stoop so low.
Elan, let's go from here.
Please.
Please, stay here.
Please don't leave me.
I will be shattered.
Please don't go.
You played
the exact same drama with me too.
Amma's love is the purest.
But if you faked that,
what kind of amma you are?
Elan, let's leave.
She is my amma.
My amma.
Say sorry to her first.
Your amma has to apologise. Not me.
My amma has never spoken ill of you
since we got married.
Because I never did anything wrong.
If you have a reason for everything,
then my amma must have her reasons too.
What justification?
Forcing me to leave my job?
Or separating me from my amma and appa?
I also came to your house
leaving my family. Understand it.
Elan, I never lied
or tricked you to my house.
I told the truth and called you.
We're not going to force you to stay here.
You can leave if you want.
Elan, if I leave now, I will not return.
If you leave now,
don't expect me to follow, Pavi.
Pavi…
Hey lady
You're taking my heart along
My love
You're killing my love as you walk away
DAD - UNCLE - AUNTY
Hey, my pains
You keep wounding me
Tell me, love
I see my dreams getting shattered
Pyaar, prema, kaadhal
Now a days, he comes home very late.
What did I do wrong?
My son has suffered so much
at their house.
I don't think it will work out.
I think it is best for them both
to part ways.
The hardship you mention is what I've been
doing here for the past ten years.
What's so hard about it?
My husband goes out to work
for the family's sake.
I labour inside the house
for the same family.
Is there any rule that says who should
stay at home and who should go to work?
You want them to part ways because
you think your son is having a hard time.
If my amma thought like that,
what would've happened to us?
It's jaggery coffee.
I'm not doing this because you like it.
I do this because I like you.
What? If I'm tired after doing chores,
won't you press my feet?
Have your coffee.
Love
Is my love
Meant to be forgotten
You one word kills me
Like a death sentence
I have no words left to say
The silence grows longer
Do not walk away
Lady'll be left alone
I'd ask another birth…
Pavi, haven't you slept yet?
…to be with you
You thought you will change the system,
but unknowingly
you also started following the same.
If a man says a woman
doesn't need to work
is considered male chauvinism,
then what are you doing?
It doesn't have a name, right?
Think about it.
Pyaar, prema, kaadhal
I hate you
and Elan too.
I like it when you two are together.
If you'd gone to live with your husband
after marriage like other girls,
I wouldn't have felt bad.
Because every amma knows
that her daughter will move out one day.
But the groom's parents
wouldn't have thought that way.
Had I been in their place,
I would not let him go with you.
You may not understand it now.
When you become a mother,
you'll understand.
We didn't get you married
to the girl you love
to watch you
and our family suffer like this.
Looking at things, I now fear
your amma may get a real heart attack.
Your decisions against me
have never really worked out.
Listen to me at least from now on.
Get married again.
-Appa, I don't want to--
-Enough.
I'll make the right decision for you.
If you move with us,
your parents will suffer.
If I move in with them, I will suffer.
I wish we had never even met here.
Do what makes your family happy.
What have you done
You crushed my heart
Cajole me a little
And tell me your love
You are the sky
You are the earth
You are my life, lady
Even if you chase me
I wouldn't go…
I feel sorry for your friend.
…I'm seeing love…
Not only him.
You are also suffering with me.
Don't be naughty.
Can we go for a Thailand trip?
Love you, dear.
Baby, we're meant to
get married just once, right?
It's in your hand, baby.
Hi, sweethearts.
Now you are watching the second marriage
of our favourite influencer
Purple Pavi's ex-husband,
live from here.
Are you ready?
It's party time.
Nirmala, is it finally turning out
the way I wanted?
Bring the bride please.
Chinnu.
What?
What are you staring at?
Stop portraying your appa as a villain.
I was your age once. I faced it.
I was acting strict because
I wanted you to become responsible.
The minute you went to
Pavi's house, you proved it.
Thank her first.
The other day, I said too much
in the heat of the moment.
Sorry.
Nobody finds it odd when a woman
moves into her husband's house.
But everyone finds it odd when a man
moves into his wife's house.
In the process of finding an answer,
I don't want to lose the one I love.
Elan loves you all.
Despite that,
he left everything behind to live
in my house because of his love for me.
Now I'm going to do this
to prove my love for him.
-I will move in with you all.
-You go home.
This time, I will come
and invite you traditionally.
You both married earlier against my wish.
Now let the same thing
happen with my blessings.
Tie the knot.
Tie the knot!
-She has one already.
-How many knots you put then?
-Three.
-Do you know the meaning of those?
The first knot signifies
that the couple must care for each other.
The second signifies that both families
should support one another.
The third knot signifies that
the groom's family must take
good care of the bride.
Now the fourth.
If the groom moves in
with the bride's family,
they should take good care of him.
Super.
I'll tie it now!
Apply the vermilion too.
"Are you okay, Ammu?
-Boss, take that right.
-App shows straight, sir.
I'm on the right route.
Don't I know the way to my home?
Take the right.
You appa told me not to listen to you.
He asked me to follow the map.
Dear, come inside.
Come.
Come in.
This is where you are going to live.
A new house bought for your wedding.
Our old house is small for our big family.
What you said the other day
was right, dear.
Showering love on one's own child alone
will not make a good amma.
You are no different to me from Elan.
We do not intend you
to leave your parents.
Come, come.
Here we are all going to live together.
Come.
PYAAR, PREMA, KAADHAL HOUSE
Wow. This is something new.
Super ending.
What is new in this?
Joint families have been around for ages!
Do you know what a joint family is?
It's about the bride alone joining
the groom's extended family.
Got it?
Gosh! From now on,
every girl will demand this, right?
Who on earth came up with this?
Thief, catch him!
-See, he is there.
-Where?
-He jumped over and is running off.
-Where did these two disappear?
Run fast.
Let's escape from their torture.
-Chinnu.
-Who will give the medicines to your appa?
-Don't worry. Amma will take care.
-Okay.
-If your amma falls sick?
-My appa will take care.
Let us worry about our life first.
They trouble us a lot.
Instead, you and I can torture each other.
Run fast, else they'll catch us.
Subtitle translation by: Shobana Raju,
Venkat Krishnamachari, Sobana Sundar